JULIE PUECH

INTERACTIVE MEDIA DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

www.juliecapucine.github.io

BIOGRAPHY

Curious, hardworking and a team-player - three words I would use to define myself. I come from a scientific background but now enjoy creating and implementing interactive experiences. I am particularly invested in exploring the world of Augmented and Mixed Reality and all the opportunities it has opened up.

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2017 - August 2017

LES CARTONS

Front-end development, Web Design, Social Media Communication

January 2018 - April 2018

YUMEBAU

Augmented Reality Development, Unity 3D scripting

PROJECTS /

INTERACTIVE DELAUNAY'S DREAMS

An installation exploring the link between human interaction, sound and visuals.

Exhibited at ArtLease, Paris in April 2018 delaunaysinteractivedreams.github.io

MUSIC HOLOGRAMS & BELLE GAME

An interactive Mixed Reality experience in collaboration with the band **BELLE GAME**, for one performance of the song "YUH" using Microsoft HoloLens and iPhones.

Showcase at Art installations exhibit at the Center for Digital Media, Vancouver in August 2018

http://blogs.thecdm.ca/visuality/

CONTACT

778 751 9544

julie_puech@thecdm.ca

#412 - 685 Great Northern Way, Vancouver, BC V5T 0C6 Canada

LANGUAGES

FRENCH native speaker

ENGLISH full professional proficency

SKILLS

DEVELOPMENT

• • • XR development

C/C++/C#

• • • Unity

• • • Processing

DESIGN

Illustrator
Photoshop
InDesign

After Effect

EDUCATION

MASTER OF DIGITAL MEDIA

Vancouver, Canada 2017 - 2019

IMAC Engineer

(equivalent to a Master degree in Art and Science)
Paris, France
2015 - 2019